/*-----------------------------Questions for Master Level------------------------*/
/*-------------------------------------------------------------------------------*/
window.gameMasterLevelQuestions = [
    {
        question: "If 35% of x = 140, 20% of x = ?",
        answerArray: ["9.8", "39.2", "80", "320"],
        matchedValue: "80",
        correctAnswer: "80",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "The number of seconds in a year?",
        answerArray: ["3.154e+8", "3.154e+7", "3.154e+9", "3.154e+6"],
        matchedValue: "3.154e+7",
        correctAnswer: "3.154e+7",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "&radic;(-9) = ?",
        answerArray: ["-3", "3i", "-3i", "3"],
        matchedValue: "3i",
        correctAnswer: "3i",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "800.5 * (2 * 10^6)",
        answerArray: ["1.601e9", "1.7e7", "1.601e9", "1.7e9"],
        matchedValue: "1.601e9",
        correctAnswer: "1.601e9",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "200 meters = ? miles",
        answerArray: ["124", "12.4", "0.124", "1.24"],
        matchedValue: "0.124",
        correctAnswer: "0.124",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "36 km/h = ? m/sec",
        answerArray: ["18", "6", "10", "100"],
        matchedValue: "10",
        correctAnswer: "10",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "The mean of first ten even natural numbers is?",
        answerArray: ["9", "10", "11", "12"],
        matchedValue: "11",
        correctAnswer: "11",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "The average of first five multiples of 3?",
        answerArray: ["3", "9", "12", "15"],
        matchedValue: "9",
        correctAnswer: "9",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "&radic;(25/81 - 1/9)",
        answerArray: ["2/3", "4/9", "16/81", "25/81"],
        matchedValue: "4/9",
        correctAnswer: "4/9",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "28&radic;? + 1426 = 3/4 of 2872",
        answerArray: ["576", "676", "1296", "1444"],
        matchedValue: "676",
        correctAnswer: "676",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "The H.C.F of 0 and 6 is?",
        answerArray: ["0", "3", "6", "Undefined"],
        matchedValue: "Undefined",
        correctAnswer: "Undefined",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "The fraction equivalent to 0.4% is?",
        answerArray: ["1/40", "1/125", "1/250", "1/500"],
        matchedValue: "1/250",
        correctAnswer: "1/250",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "?/529 = 329/?",
        answerArray: ["404", "408", "414", "416"],
        matchedValue: "416",
        correctAnswer: "416",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "x/5 - x/6 = 4. Find x.",
        answerArray: ["-120", "-100", "100", "120"],
        matchedValue: "120",
        correctAnswer: "120",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "What fraction of an hour is a second?",
        answerArray: ["1/24", "1/60", "1/120", "1/3600"],
        matchedValue: "1/3600",
        correctAnswer: "1/3600",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "1.5x = 0.04y, (y-x)/(y+x) = ?",
        answerArray: ["730/77", "73/77", "7.3/77", "7.3/7.7"],
        matchedValue: "73/77",
        correctAnswer: "73/77",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "144/0.144 = 14.4/x, x = ?",
        answerArray: ["0.0144", "1.44", "14.4", "144"],
        matchedValue: "0.0144",
        correctAnswer: "0.0144",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "(0.05 * 5 - 0.005 * 5) = ?",
        answerArray: ["0.0225", "0.225", "0.250", "0.275"],
        matchedValue: "0.225",
        correctAnswer: "0.225",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: "b/a = 0.25, (2a-b/2a+b) + 2/9 = ?",
        answerArray: ["0", "2", "9", "1"],
        matchedValue: "1",
        correctAnswer: "1",
        isVisited: 0
    },
    {
        question: ".4 * .04 * .004 * 40 = ?",
        answerArray: [".02560", "2.560", ".002560", "25.60"],
        matchedValue: ".002560",
        correctAnswer: ".002560",
        isVisited: 0
    }
];